Halloween the game has six challenges
per single player story chapter. In case
you're having any trouble, here's how
you complete them in chapter 5.
Challenge one, use blackout to disable
two cop flashlights at once. Get the
attention of a few cops and slam your
blackout ability, the best album by
Britney.
Challenge two, kill a cop with a
pitchfork execution. Weapon spawn with
RNG here, so you might have to look
around a little bit. The best tip here
is once you gain back your abilities
with bloodthirst by killing enough
inhabitants in the level, first person
stalk will help pinpoint weapons around
the environment. I found one here.
Once you have a pitchfork, execute a
cop.
Challenge three, kill at least three
other residents before escaping.
Check the houses with question marks on
your map and take out the inhabitants.
>> [groaning]
>> Challenge four, fully stalk any police
in the Wallace's house. Look at the
house where Annie was babysitting and
find a cop within. Stalk them to three
and you'll get this challenge.
Challenge five, escape without Loomis
detecting you.
Dr. Loomis is perpetually watching the
neighborhood, but he is easy to avoid so
long as you check your map here and
there for the big red smudge. Avoid that
and you'll avoid him.
Otherwise, complete the level.
There are multiple possible endings, so
follow the waypoint and go where it
tells you.
Challenge six, destroy any police car
before you escape.
Several police cars are stationed around
the suburbs. Simply slap them around
with your melee attack and you'll
demolish it. Complete the level and you
got it.
>> She's down in the gully.
>> And that's all the challenges in chapter
five. Happy hunting in Haddonfield.